Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 10, 1.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, October 19, 1938; 17.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, October 26, 1938; 18.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Minutes, November 2, 1938; 1.
    - Helio Kennedy to Julius Emspak, November 4, 1938; 2.
    - Harry Bullock to Emspak, November 7, 1938; 3.
    - Minutes, November 16, 1938; 4.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, November 16, 1938; 5.
    - Emspak to Bullock, November 22, 1938; 6.
    - Helio Kennedy to William Mitchell, November 23, 1938; 7.
    - Bullock to Emspak, December 9, 1938; 8.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, December 10, 1938; 9.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, December 13, 1938; 10.
    - Mitchell to Helio Kennedy, December 16, 1938; 11.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, December 21, 1938; 12.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Mitchell, January 6, 1938; 13.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Matles, January 6, 1939; 14.
    - Mitchell to Vernon Kennedy, January 9, 1939; 15.
    - Matles to Helio Kennedy, January 9, 1939; 16.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, January 6, 1939; 17.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, January 10, 1939; 18.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, January 13, 1939; 19.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Vernon Kennedy to Julius Emspak, January 16, 1939; 1.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, January 16, 1939; 2.
    - Harry Bullock to Emspak, February 1, 1939; 3.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, February 10, 1939; 4.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, February 16, 1939; 5.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, February 22, 1939; 6.
    - Helio Kennedy to J.F. Murphy, February 22, 1939; 7.
    - Fischer Corporation to Vernon Kennedy, February 23, 1939; 8.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, February 24, 1939; 9.
    - Minutes, March 1, 1939; 10.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, March 3, 1939; 11.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, March 15, 1939; 12.
    - Minutes, March 15, 1939; 13.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, March 15, 1939; 14.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, March 17, 1939; 15.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, March 20, 1939; 16.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, March 22, 1939; 17.
    - Bullock to Emspak, March 23, 1939; 18.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, March 25, 1939; 19.
    - Emspak to Bullock, April 15, 1939; 20.
    - Bullock to Emspak, April 12, 1939; 21.
    - Emspak to Bullock, April 17, 1939; 22.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Minutes, April 19, 1939; 1.
    - Harry Bullock to Julius Emspak, April 23, 1939; 2.
    - Helio Kennedy to James Matles, May 22, 1939; 3.
    - Financial Statement, May 1939; 4.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, July 1939; 5.
    - Bullock to Emspak, August 7, 1939; 6.
    - Constitution with August 7, 1939, Helio Kennedy Letter to Congress of Industrial Organizations, August 1939; 7.
    - Helio Kennedy to Matles, August 8, 1939; 8.
    - Matles to Helio Kennedy, August 11, 1939; 9.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, August 17, 1939; 10.
    - Walter Smethtorst to Allan Haywood, August 21, 1939; 11.
    - Haywood to Emspak with August 24, 1939, Haywood Letter to Smethurst, 12.
    - Helio Kennedy to Matles, August 25, 1939; 13.
    - Emspak to Bullock, August 25, 1939; 14.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, August 28, 1939; 15.
    - Matles to Helio Kennedy, August 31, 1939; 16.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, September 1, 1939; 17.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, September 12, 1939; 18.
    - R.E. Reeder to Matles, September 20, 1939; 19.
    - Minutes, October 30, 1939; 20.
    - Minutes, October 18, 1939; 21.
    - Minutes, October 25, 1939; 22.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, October 3, 1939; 23.
  - District 10 Los Angeles Projectionists Organization, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Blair Fletcher to John Lewis, May 30, 1939; 1.
    - James Matles to Fletcher, June 12, 1939; 2.
  - District 10 Washington Electricians Organization, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Norman Murray to UE, May 25, 1939; 1.
    - James Matles to Murray, June 3, 1939; 2.
    - Ray Moon to John Lewis, August 3, 1939; 3.
    - J.R. Bell to James Carey, September 8, 1939; 4.
    - Matles to Moon, September 12, 1939; 5.
  - District 10 Machine Transfer and Steelworkers Organizing Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - G. Stefler to James Matles, December 12, 1939; 1.
    - Matles to James Smith, February 19, 1940; 2.
    - Julius Emspak to Smith, February 27, 1940; 3.
    - Letter to John Flannery, February 29, 1940; 4.
    - David McDonald to Emspak, March 4, 1940; 5.
    - McDonald to Emspak, March 9, 1940; 6.
    - Smith to Matles, March 9, 1940; 7.
    - Emspak to Leo Turner, March 12, 1940; 8.
    - Emspak to Smith, March 20, 1940; 9.
    - Matles to Smith, March 24, 1940; 10.
  - District 10 Carl Brant Bay Area Organization, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - James Matles to Carl Brant, April 24, 1942; 1.
    - Brant to Matles, May 2, 1942; 2.
    - Brant to Matles, May 16, 1942; 3.
    - Brant to Matles, May 24, 1942; 4.
    - Brant to Matles, May 27, 1942; 5.
    - Julius Emspak to Brant, June 3, 1942; 6.
    - Brant to Matles, June 5, 1942; 7.
    - Brant to Matles, June 6, 1942; 8.
    - Matles to Brant, June 9, 1942; 9.
    - Brant to Matles, June 27, 1942; 10.
    - Matles to Brant, June 30, 1942; 11.
    - Matles to Brant, August 17, 1942; 12.
    - Matles to Brant, August 21, 1942; 13.
    - Brant to Matles, August 25, 1942; 14.
    - Brant to Matles, August 24, 1942; 15.
    - Matles to Brant, August 27, 1942; 16.
    - Neil Brant to Carl Brant with Wage Incentive Plan, Telegram, and Vacancy Memo, September 8, 1942; 17.
  - District 10 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak, April 19, 1943; 1.
    - Emspak to Turner, April 23, 1943; 2.
  - District 10 Locals List, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - John Dalton Letter, March 22, 1943; 1.
    - Dalton to Julius Emspak, April 16, 1943; 2.
    - Emspak to Dalton, April 27, 1943; 3.
  - District 10 Martin Hourihan Monthly Reports, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Martin Hourihan to Julius Emspak, November 1943; 1.
    - Hourihan to Emspak, December 1943; 2.
  - District 10 William Sentner Reports, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Memo, February 1, 1944; 1.
    - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, February 7, 1944; 2.
    - Sentner to Emspak, February 7, 1944; 3.
    - Organization Plan for Los Angeles, February 7, 1944; 4.
    - Organizational Program for California, February 7, 1944; 5.
    - Sentner to David Scribner, February 8, 1944; 6.
    - Sentner to Emspak, February 8, 1944; 7.
  - District 10 Carl Brant Organizers Reports, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Carl Brant to Julius Emspak, February 19, 1945; 1.
    - Brant to Emspak, May 22, 1945; 2.
  - District 10 Political Action, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - William Elconin to Russ Nixon with Southern California PAC Conference Minutes, September 11, 1947; 1.
    - Elconin to Nixon, September 16, 1947; 2.
    - Elconin to Nixon, October 15, 1947; 3.
    - Elconin to Nixon, December 17, 1947; 4.
    - California Congress Members Election Statistics, December 1947; 5.
    - Nixon to Elconin, January 8, 1948; 6.
    - Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald, March 29, 1948; 7.
  - District 10 Southern California Conference Minutes, January 30-September 24, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - District 10 Southern California Conference Minutes, October 22, 1948-May 27, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - District 10 Southern California Conference Minutes, January 24, 1949-February 24, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - District 10 Pacific Coast Conference, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - William Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald, July 12, 1948; 1.
    - Elconin to James Matles, July 27, 1948; 2.
  - District 10 District Council Charter, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - William Elconin to Julius Emspak, November 14, 1950; 1.
    - Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald, January 24, 1951; 2.
    - Petition, February 1951; 3.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald, April 6, 1951; 4.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald, April 10, 1951; 5.
    - Local 1412 to General Executive Board, April 13, 1951; 6.
    - Carl Brant to Fitzgerald, April 27, 1951; 7.
    - James Matles to Elconin, June 5, 1951; 8.
  - District 10 Saturday Evening Post, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - William Elconin to Stewards, October 17, 1952; 1.
    - Elconin to Stewards, October 27, 1952; 2.
  - District 10 Albert Fitzgerald Visit, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - William Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald, March 7, 1955; 1.
    - Fitzgerald to Elconin, March 24, 1955; 2.
  - District 10 Correspondence and Reports, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Herbert Carlson to UE, December 17, 1936; 1.
    - Officers List, May 4, 1937; 2.
    - Local Addresses, May 17, 1937; 3.
    - Robert Shippey Report Regarding Finances, September 31, 1937; 4.
    - Ruth to Al Stonkus Regarding Finances, November 30, 1937; 5.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Albert Stonkus Regarding Southern California Gas Contract, January 9, 1938; 6.
    - Kennedy to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 12, 1938; 7.
    - Emspak to Kennedy Regarding Finances, January 13, 1938; 8.
    - Kennedy to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 15, 1938; 9.
    - James Matles to Electrical Manufacturing Locals, March 4, 1938; 10.
    - Richard Francis to Emspak Regarding Western Electric Organization, April 25, 1938; 11.
    - Joint California Meeting Minutes, July 10, 1938; 12.
  - District 10 Correspondence and Minutes, 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Pre State Congress of Industrial Organizations Conference, August 19, 1938; 1.
    - James Matles to Leo Turner Regarding Staff Members, January 15, 1942; 2.
    - Women in Industry Conference Minutes, June 28, 1942; 3.
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, December 11, 1943; 4.
    - Irene Robinson to Julius Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor and Utility Fan with February 1, 1944, Federated Press Article, January 21, 1944; 5.
    - Carl Brant to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, March 13, 1944; 6.
  - District 10 Records on Staff and Organizing, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Philip Connelly to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Members, December 23, 1944; 1.
    - Organizers Weekly Report, January 6, 1945; 2.
    - Disposition of Staff, October 1, 1945; 3.
    - Organization Status, 1945; 4.
    - Organization Report, October 1945; 5.
    - Roy Atkinson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Westinghouse Seattle Organization, January 19, 1946; 6.
    - Memo Regarding California Conferences with Southern California Organization Program; Summaries of Locals 1421, 1412 and 1012; and San Francisco Organization, May 17, 1946; 7.
    - James Matles to California Locals Regarding Staff Members, July 8, 1946; 8.
  - District 10 Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Contract Status, May 7, 1947; 1.
    - Contract Status, May 14, 1947; 2.
    - William Elconin to District Executive Board Members, June 26, 1947; 3.
    - Russ Nixon to Philip Connolly Regarding Los Angeles Congress of Industrial Organizations, September 4, 1947; 4.
    - James Matles to All Field Organization Regarding Staff Members, November 13, 1947; 5.
    - Elconin to Matles Regarding Staff Members with Shop List and Per Capita, December 8, 1947; 6.
    - California CIO Resolution Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 12, 1948; 7.
    - Elconin to Local Executive Board Members Regarding Red-baiting with Press Release, September 30, 1948; 8.
    - Los Angeles CIO Resolution Regarding Taft Hartley, October 1, 1948; 9.
    - Elconin to Matles Regarding Local 1412, Factionalism, and Staff Members, January 24, 1949; 10.
    - Elconin to California UE Conference Members Regarding Factionalism, September 9, 1949; 11.
    - Elconin to California UE Conference Members Regarding CIO Inter-union Rivalry, November 11, 1949; 12.
  - District 10 Correspondence, 1949-1955 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - William Elconin to California Conference Members Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Inter-union Rivalry, November 23, 1949; 1.
    - Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, November 29, 1949; 2.
    - Elconin to California Conference Members Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1, 1949; 3.
    - Petition Regarding Fitzgerald Visit and Inter-union Rivalry, April 5, 1950; 4.
    - Louise Harding to Justice Balck Regarding Smith Act with Book Excerpts, June 21, 1951; 5.
    - Per Capita List, 1951; 6.
    - Elconin to James Matles Regarding Officers Visit, February 10, 1953; 7.
    - Fitzgerald to Elconin Regarding District Convention, October 15, 1953; 8.
    - Matles to Elconin Regarding Per Capita, January 25, 1954; 9.
    - Julius Emspak to Elconin, February 24, 1954; 10.
    - Fitzgerald to Clara Fiering Regarding Local 1418, October 27, 1954; 11.
    - Emspak to Elconin Regarding Mill Town, December 13, 1954; 12.
    - Elconin to Emspak Regarding Address Change, December 8, 1955; 13.
  - District 10 Correspondence, 1967-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - District 10 Correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - District 10 Constitutions, 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - District 10 Constitutions, 1951-1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - District 10 Reports on Local Dues and Per Capita Increase, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - District 10 Temporary Organization and District Arrangements, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - District 10 Miscellaneous, 1967-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - District 10 Monies and Other Subsidies, 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - District 10 Letters to Affiliate UE and IUE, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - District 10 Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - District 10 Minutes, 1980-1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - District 10 Mimeo Material, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - District 10 Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - District 10 Correspondence, 1971-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - District 10 Dura Vent, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - District 10 Gertrude S. Southern Correspondence, 1963-1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - District 10 Mary McDaniel Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - District 10 Charters, 1943-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - District 10 California Mimeo, 1956-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - District 10 California Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - District 10 Neal Eastman Correspondence, 1949-1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - District 10 Grant Willis Ebersole Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - District 10 Howard J. Edelson Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - District 10 James C. Egri Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - District 10 William Elconin Correspondence, 1948-1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - District 10 Alfred Ellis Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - District 10 Forest D. Emerson Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - District 10 Michael Evkovich Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - District 10 National Semi-Conductor Electronics Organization, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- District 10 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1002
    - Local 1002 Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Julius Emspak to John Keith Regarding Organization, March 8, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to R. Hjelmaa Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 21, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Rollin Davis Regarding Strike, December 20, 1955; 3.
      - James Matles to Robert Simon Regarding 1955 UE Convention, September 9, 1955; 4.
    - Local 1002 Outgoing Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Richard Downing to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Political Action, April 10, 1948; 1.
      - Joseph Mesich to UE Regarding Strike Fund, November 16, 1952; 2.
      - Robert Simon to James Matles Regarding Grievances and 1955 UE Convention, August 6, 1955; 3.
    - Local 1002 Organization, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Harry Tucker to Albert Fitzgerald, March 2, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Tucker, March 8, 1946; 2.
      - Tucker to Emspak, June 21, 1946; 3.
      - William Elconin to Emspak, June 21, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Tucker, July 1, 1946; 5.
    - Local 1002 UE Convention, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - ELM Memo to Dave Ratner, June 13, 1955; 1.
      - Emma Memo to Ray, August 11, 1955; 2.
    - Local 1002 Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - William Elconin to Edward Matthews Regarding Seattle Visit and Grievances, January 21, 1948; 1.
      - Elconin to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 11, 1948; 2.
      - James Matles to Elconin Regarding Negotiations and International Longshore and Warehouse Union with Credential, January 29, 1954; 3.
      - Matles to Pete Abbond Regarding Grievances, August 9, 1955; 4.
      - Emspak to Sarah Lesser Regarding Finances, December 20, 1955; 5.
    - Local 1002 Seattle Westinghouse Electric Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Local 1002 Seattle, WA, 1956-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local 1004
    - Local 1004 Membership Resolution Regarding Factionalism and Hartley Committee, October 5, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Local 1004 Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Julius Emspak to Jackie Horton Regarding Organization, April 22, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Joseph Hogan Regarding Taft Hartley Affidavit, January 19, 1950; 2.
    - Local 1004 Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - George Cessna to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes, February 24, 1948; 1.
      - Cessna to Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes, February 26, 1948; 2.
      - Ben Davis to Tom Wright Regarding UE News and Contracts, November 25, 1953; 3.
      - Davis to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, April 21, 1955; 4.
      - Joseph Hogan to Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, November 21, 1947; 5.
      - Hogan to Emspak Regarding Smith Meter Amalgamation and Local 1421, December 27, 1950; 6.
    - Local 1004 Publications, UE 1004 News, June 24, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Local 1004 Sawyer Electric Organization, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - William Elconin to James Matles, March 28, 1947; 1.
      - Matles to Elconin, March 29, 1947; 2.
      - Elconin to Julius Emspak, April 18, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Elconin, April 22, 1947; 4.
      - Elconin to Emspak, May 14, 1947; 5.
    - Local 1004 Per Capita Payments, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - William Elconin to Julius Emspak, May 13, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Elconin, May 17, 1948; 2.
    - Local 1004 A.O. Smith Strike, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Julius Emspak to William Elconin, June 7, 1948; 1.
      - Elconin to Emspak, June 9, 1948; 2.
      - Petition with Letters to General Executive Board, June 7, 1948; 3.
      - Emspak to Elconin, July 1, 1948; 4.
      - Elconin to Emspak, July 1, 1948; 5.
      - Emspak to Elconin, July 9, 1948; 6.
      - Elconin to Emspak, July 19, 1948; 7-8.
      - Elconin to Emspak, July 30, 1948; 9.
    - Local 1004 Correspondence, William Elconin to James Matles Regarding Taft Hartley Affidavits, January 16, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Local 1004 Los Angeles Sawyer Electrical Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Local 1004 710 Forms, 1947-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Local 1005
    - Local 1005 Officers List, April 7, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Local 1005 Incoming Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Julius Emspak to Marjorie Strange Regarding Organization, August 25, 1947; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to William Erickson Regarding Red-baiting and Factionalism with Newspaper Clippings, November 12, 1947; 2.
    - Local 1005 Outgoing Correspondence, William Erickson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Red-baiting and Factionalism with Newspaper Clippings, October 26, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Local 1005 Organization (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - William Elconin to James Matles, June 19, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Elconin, June 20, 1947; 2.
      - Majorie Strange Memo, August 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Elconin, August 25, 1947; 4.
    - Local 1005 Disbanding, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Julius Emspak to William Elconin, March 4, 1948; 1.
      - Elconin to Emspak, March 8, 1948; 2.
  - Local 1006
    - Local 1006 Officers Lists, November 1946-August 18, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Local 1006 Incoming Correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - T. Arden to Local 1006 Regarding Negotiations and Red-baiting, May 28, 1948; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Charles Hellman Regarding Organization, March 11, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Mildred Siendge Regarding Dues, January 26, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Fred Serrell Regarding Per Capita and Strikes, March 26, 1946; 4.
    - Local 1006 Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Thomas Beam to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, December 23, 1944; 1.
      - Gertrude Bottam to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 24, 1948; 2.
      - Mildred Sieuridge to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, July 16, 1947; 3.
      - Sieuridge to Emspak Regarding Finances with Resolution, August 18, 1948; 4.
      - Fred Sewell to Emspak Regarding Strikes, March 18, 1946; 5.
    - Local 1006 Leaflets, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - T. Arden to Local 1006 Regarding Negotiations and Red-baiting, May 17, 1948; 1.
      - Grayson Management to Grayson Workers Regarding Red-baiting, May 20, 1948; 2.
      - Letter to All Shop Employees Regarding United Auto Workers, AFC, and Company Union Inter-union Rivalry, June 16, 1948; 3.
      - "Alden Tries To Be Dictator" Regarding UAW, AFC, and Company Union Inter-union Rivalry, June 16, 1948; 4.
      - "You Can Stop This" Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry, June 21, 1948; 5.
      - "Here Are The Facts" Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry, June 1948; 6.
    - Local 1006 Pamphlet Regarding Red-baiting with Grayson Management Letter to Grayson Workers, May 17, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Local 1006 Separate Charter, Union Committee to Julius Emspak with Charter Members List and Poll, December 1943 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Local 1006 Separate Charter, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Julius Emspak to Martin Hourihan, December 27, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Hourihan, January 7, 1944; 2.
      - William Sentner to Emspak with Local 1421 Grayson Shop Stipulation of Agreement, February 7, 1944; 3.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Sentner, February 21, 1944; 4.
      - O.W. Larson to Sentner, March 4, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Sentner, March 11, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Carl Brant, March 11, 1944; 7.
      - Brant to T.T. Arden, May 18, 1944; 8.
    - Local 1006 Strike, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Carl Brant to James Matles, November 23, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Brant, November 30, 1945; 2.
      - Report of Strike, January 9, 1946; 3.
      - Termination of Strike, April 4, 1946; 4.
    - Local 1006 Inter-union Rivalry and Disbanding, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Len Titelman to James Matles, June 8, 1948; 1.
      - Titelman to Matles, June 16, 1948; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to William Elconin, June 6, 1949; 3.
      - Elconin to Emspak, June 27, 1949; 4.
      - Memo, June 27, 1949; 5.
    - Local 1006 Correspondence, William Elconin to Julius Emspak, February 11, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Local 1007
    - Local 1007 Officers Lists, April 2, 1953-March 1954 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Local 1007 Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Oscar Jardin Regarding Organization, July 24, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Local 1007 Outgoing Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - M.C. Crews to James Matles Regarding Dues and Staff Members, July 26, 1954; 1.
      - Sylvia Thomas to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 25, 1951; 2.